{
	"q1": {
		"question": "HTML stands for?",
		"options": [
			"Hyper Text Markup Language",
			"High Text Markup Language",
			"Hyper Tabular Markup Language",
			"None of these"
		],
		"answer": "Hyper Text Markup Language",
		"type": "html"
	},
	"q2": {
		"question": "which of the following tag is used to mark a begining of paragraph ?",
		"options": [
			"<TD>",
			"<br>",
			"<P>",
			"<TR>"
		],
		"answer": "<P>",
		"type": "html"
	},
	"q3": {
		"question": "From which tag descriptive list starts ?",
		"options": [
			"<LL>",
			"<DD>",
			"<DL>",
			"<DS>"
		],
		"answer": "<DL>",
		"type": "html"
	},
	"q4": {
		"question": "Correct HTML tag for the largest heading is",
		"options": [
			"<head>",
			"<h6>",
			"<heading>",
			"<h1>"
		],
		"answer": "<h1>",
		"type": "html"
	},
	"q5": {
		"question": "The attribute of <form> tag",
		"options": [
			"Method",
			"Action",
			"Both (a)&(b)",
			"None of these"
		],
		"answer": "Both (a)&(b)",
		"type": "html"
	},
	"q6": {
		"question": "www is based on which model?",
		"options": [
			"Local-server",
			"Client-server",
			"3-tier",
			"None of these"
		],
		"answer": "Client-server",
		"type": "html"
	},
	"q7": {
		"question": "Markup tags tell the web browser",
		"options": [
			"How to organise the page",
			"How to display the page",
			"How to display message box on page",
			"None of these"
		],
		"answer": "How to display the page",
		"type": "html"
	},
	"q8": {
		"question": "What are Empty elements and is it valid?",
		"options": [
			"No, there is no such terms as Empty Element",
			"Empty elements are element with no data",
			"No, it is not valid to use Empty Element",
			"None of these"
		],
		"answer": "Empty elements are element with no data",
		"type": "html"
	},
	"q9": {
		"question": "Which of the following attributes of text box control allow to limit the maximum character?",
		"options": [
			"size",
			"len",
			"maxlength",
			"all of these"
		],
		"answer": "maxlength",
		"type": "html"
	},
	"q10": {
		"question": "Web pages starts with which ofthe following tag?",
		"options": [
			"<Body>",
			"<Title>",
			"<HTML>",
			"<Form>"
		],
		"answer": "<HTML>",
		"type": "html"
	}
}